const questions = [
  {
    question: "1 + 1",
    answers: {
      a: "2",
      b: "5",
      c: "1"
    },
    correctAnswer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "2 + 2",
    answers: {
      a: "5",
      b: "8",
      c: "4"
    },
    correctAnswer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: "3 + 3",
    answers: {
      a: "9",
      b: "6",
      c: "3"
    },
    correctAnswer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: "4 + 4",
    answers: {
      a: "8",
      b: "16",
      c: "4"
    },
    correctAnswer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: "5 + 5",
    answers: {
      a: "10",
      b: "5",
      c: "15"
    },
    correctAnswer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: "6 + 6",
    answers: {
      a: "12",
      b: "36",
      c: "16"
    },
    correctAnswer: "12"
  },
  {
    question: "7 + 7",
    answers: {
      a: "14",
      b: "7",
      c: "21"
    },
    correctAnswer: "14"
  },
  {
    question: "8 + 8",
    answers: {
      a: "16",
      b: "18",
      c: "64"
    },
    correctAnswer: "16"
  },
  {
    question: "9 + 9",
    answers: {
      a: "18",
      b: "21",
      c: "19"
    },
    correctAnswer: "18"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 2",
    answers: {
      a: "2",
      b: "3",
      c: "1"
    },
    correctAnswer: "3"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 3",
    answers: {
      a: "4",
      b: "3",
      c: "2"
    },
    correctAnswer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 4",
    answers: {
      a: "5",
      b: "3",
      c: "4"
    },
    correctAnswer: "5"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 5",
    answers: {
      a: "6",
      b: "4",
      c: "5"
    },
    correctAnswer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 6",
    answers: {
      a: "7",
      b: "6",
      c: "5"
    },
    correctAnswer: "7"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 7",
    answers: {
      a: "7",
      b: "8",
      c: "6"
    },
    correctAnswer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 8",
    answers: {
      a: "9",
      b: "7",
      c: "8"
    },
    correctAnswer: "9"
  },
  {
    question: "1 + 9",
    answers: {
      a: "10",
      b: "9",
      c: "8"
    },
    correctAnswer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: "2 + 1",
    answers: {
      a: "3",
      b: "1",
      c: "2"
    },
    correctAnswer: "3"
  },
  {
    question: "2 + 2",
    answers: {
      a: "4",
      b: "3",
      c: "1"
    },
    correctAnswer: "4"
  }
];

export default questions;
